{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Caine",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Rotherhithe",
    "human_readable": "Michael Caine was born in Rotherhithe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8453666567802429,
            "question": "Where was Michael Caine born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7610697150230408,
            "question": "What year was Michael Caine born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6778435111045837,
            "question": "Name the London borough where Michael Caine was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.497310996055603,
            "question": "What is Michael Caine's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3746618926525116,
            "question": "What is Michael Caine famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22454527020454407,
            "question": "In what movies did Michael Caine star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20956091582775116,
            "question": "What type of roles is Michael Caine known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17587192356586456,
            "question": "Is Michael Caine still active in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17218278348445892,
            "question": "Has Michael Caine won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1457667201757431,
            "question": "Has Michael Caine ever directed a film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Caine was born in Rotherhithe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8670_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Michael Caine won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8670_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Caine still active in the film industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8670_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles is Michael Caine known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8670_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8670_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which confirm that Michael Caine was indeed born in Rotherhithe, London."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}